# Kaustubh Joshi

# Full-Stack Software Engineer

Nashik, Maharashtra, India

#### **SUMMARY**

An experienced and resourceful full-stack software engineer, I use the tools and resources at my disposal to create system that save time, help people work more effectively and improve the overall user Experience.

Fueled by a lifelong passion for programming I have excelled in building software, from mobile app development to scaling the deployment of system in an national enterprise. I keep things as simple as possible, and create the best possible solutions with the time and resources available.

# **SKILLS**

# **Tools and Technologies:**

- Angular JS / Angular 2+
- Python (Flask/Django)
- MongoDB
- Amazon Web Services
- PHP
- Node JS
- Android
- Ionic 2+
- React Native
- MySQL
- Github
- Postman
- OrderCloud API

#### Soft Skills:

- Excellent written and verbal communication skills.
- Skilled in Teamwork, Leadership, Public Speaking.
- Adept at Problem Solving and Improvising.
- Able to Learn and Improvise skill set with E-Learning.
- Balanced mixture of flexibility and patience.

### **EXPERIENCE**

# **Archway Marketing Services, MN, US**

Full-Stack Software Engineer (Contract)

November 2018 - Present

- Work on latest technologies like Angular 7, C# to build robust Marketing Solution Applications.
- Work on Ordercloud SDK to do CRUD operation using OC services API.
- Attend Daily BA/PM meetings to discuss work progress and updates, to ensure application is getting built as per client expectations.
- Connect with other offshore member via team collaboration tools like Workplace, Join Me, Outlook and Skype.
- Use Version Control Tools like Git to ensure updated application over all developers, progress of project and deployment.
- Test application over QA clone and compare it with client requirement to ensure robustness of application.
- Use tools like GitHub/Workplace to interact with offshore team member to report any bugs or/and discuss new approaches to develop optimized solutions.

### Weoto Techlabs, Nashik, Maharashtra, IN

Co-Founder and Full-Stack Software Engineer

May 2017 - Present

- Developing User Friendly, Dynamic and Stable Software/Hardware applications over web and mobile platform.
- Intermediate Level Adobe Photoshop Skills to create icons, logos, vector assets and banners.
- Leading the projects on both technical and management fronts.
- Brainstorming with the team about new ideas to ensure the quality of product.
- Providing technical support to the clients over chats and calls
- Providing on-site assistance and consultation for products ensuring fault tolerant system.
- Demonstrating the product to the clients in order to have transparency between expectations and deliverable.
- Piloting interns with tips and tricks in projects to help them achieve their expected outcome.
- Tutoring programming enthusiast.
- Conducting seminars and Workshops at institute level.
- Attending institute level competition as Judge.

#### Solace Infotech, Nashik, Maharashtra, IN

Project Intern

June 2016 - June 2017

- Project Leader of academic Project.
- Worked on Android Native, PHP Codeigniter, Jquery, Ajax, MySQL as Full Stack Developer.

#### **EDUCATION**

# Gokhale Education Society's R.H.Sapat College of Engineering and Management Studies, Nashik - Engineering Degree

JUNE 2013 - JUNE 2017

- Participated in intercollege project competition.
- Actively Volunteered in seminar and workshop management.
- Participated in Management of small events in college.
- Volunteered in managing technical tools like music system, projector and computer system in annual college events.
- Photographer for events.
- Managed an intercollege competition at technical front.

# K.T.H.M. Arts, Science and Commerce College and Research Centre,

Nashik - Junior College, Science JUNE 2011 – JUNE 2013

# Pethe High School, Nashik - S.S.C

JUNE 2001 - JUNE 2011

- Musical performance in Annual School Event.
- Tree Plantation.
- Cleanliness Awareness Campaign.

### **HONORS AND AWARDS**

# Interaction with Dr.Mashelkar and Dr.Kakodkar sir 2018

Feb 2018, GESCOE

Demonstration of SIH Application in front of Padma Vibhushan Dr.Raghunath Mashelkar Sir and Padma vibhushan Dr.Anil kakodkar sir as Group Leader on 100th anniversary of Gokhale Education Society.

#### **Best Achievement Award 2017**

Apr 2017, Solace Infotech Pvt. Ltd.

Best Achievement Award 2017 at Solace Infotech Annual Award Ceremony.

## Winner of Smart India Hackathon 2017

Apr 2017, Ministry of Ayush, India.

Winner of Smart India Hackathon 2017 "A 36 hours nonstop coding competition" under department of Ayush,India.

# **CONTACT DETAILS**

Full Name: Mr. Kaustubh Ajay Joshi

Nationality: Indian

Date of Birth: 13 June 1996

**Contact Details:** +91-9762720307

**Email:** kaustubh.joshi136@gmail.com

Address: N-35,S-4/7/1/2,Swami Vivekanand

Nagar, Cidco, Nashik-422009

**LinkedIn**: www.linkedin.com/in/kaustubhjoshi-5432b4111